var quiz = [
  {
    question: "How many Super Bowls have the Steelers won?",
    answer: "6",
    choices: [4,5,1]
  },
  {
    question: "How many Super Bowls have the Steelers played in?",
    answer: "8",
    choices: [4,5,10]
  },
  {
    question: "Who was Super Bowl MVP in Super Bowl IX?",
    answer: "Franco Harris",
    choices: ["Terry Bradshaw", "Dwight White", "Lynn Swann"]
  },
  {
    question: "How many times have the Steelers played the Dallas Cowboys in the Super Bowl?",
    answer: "3",
    choices: [0,2,1]
  },
  {
    question: "What Steeler has the longest TD run in Super Bowl history?",
    answer: "Willie Parker",
    choices: ["Jerome Bettis", "Franco Harris", "Walter Abercrombie"]
  },
  {
    question: "Who did the Steelers defeat in Super Bowl XIV?",
    answer: "Los Angeles Rams",
    choices: ["Dallas Cowboys", "San Francisco 49ers", "Detroit Lions"]
  },
  {
    question: "How many TD passes did Ben Roethlisberger throw in Super Bowl XL?",
    answer: "0",
    choices: [5,2,1]
  },
  {
    question: "How many TD passes did WR Antwaan Randle-El throw in Super Bowl XL?",
    answer: "1",
    choices: [3,0,2]
  },
  {
    question: "Who did the Steelers defeat in Super Bowl X?",
    answer: "Dallas Cowboys",
    choices: ["Minnesota Vikings", "San Francisco 49ers", "New York Giants"]
  },
  {
    question: "What Steeler has the longest Interception TD return in Super Bowl history?",
    answer: "James Harrison",
    choices: ["Mel Blount", "Carnell Lake", "Troy Polamalu"]
  },
];

// console.log(quiz[9].choices[0]);

// export { quiz };

// export default quiz;
